modernmom.com 2019-05-07

# Privacy Policy - ModernMom

**Welcome**

Welcome to **ModernMom.com** , a website owned by Mom, Inc. This Privacy Policy is designed to tell youabout our practices regarding collection, use, and disclosure of information that you may provide via this site. Please be sure to read this entire Privacy Policy before using or submitting information to this site.

 **Your Consent**

By using this site, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and the ModernMom.com Terms of Use. Whenever you submit information via this site, you consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of that information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

 **About Children**

This site is not intended for children under the age of 13. We will not knowingly collect personally identifiable information via this site from visitors in this age group.

 **Information You Provide**

This site actively collects information from its visitors both by asking you specific questions and by permitting you to communicate directly with us via e-mail, feedback forms, and/or chat rooms. Some of the information that you submit may be personally identifiable information (that is, information that can be uniquely identified with you, such as your full name, address, e-mail address, phone number, and so on).

Some areas of this site may ask you to submit personally identifiable information in order for you to benefit from the specified features (such as newsletter subscriptions, tips/pointers, order processing, or resume submission) or to participate in a particular activity (such as sweepstakes or other promotions). You will be informed what information is required and what information is optional.

 **Passive Information Collection**

As you navigate through this site, certain anonymous information can be passively collected (that is, gathered without your actively providing the information) using various technologies, such as cookies, Internet tags or web beacons, and navigational data collection (log files, server logs, clickstream). Your Internet browser automatically transmits to this site some of this anonymous information, such as the URL of the Web site you just came from andthe Internet Protocol (IP) address and the browser version your computer is currently using. This site may also collect anonymous information from your computer through cookies and Internet tags or web beacons. You may set your browser to notify you when a cookie is sent or to refuse cookies altogether, but certain features of this site might not work without cookies.

This site may use and combine such passively collected anonymous information to provide better service to site visitors, customize the site based on your preferences, compile and analyze statistics and trends, and otherwise administer and improve the site for your use. We may at times combine personally identifiable information with passively collected information in order to personalize offers and the site for our users (for example, combined information may allow us to recommend products or features to you based on what you have liked in the past).

 **Use and Disclosure of Information**

Except as otherwise stated, we may use information collected via this site to improve the content of our site, to customize the site to your preferences, to communicate information to you (if you have requested it), for our marketing and research purposes, and for any other purpose specified. We may use personally identifiable information to contact you in relation to a transaction(e.g., we may telephone you to update you on the delivery status of an order for goods). In addition, we may make full use of all information acquired through this site that is not in personally identifiable form.

If you provide personally identifiable information to this site, we may combine such information with other actively collected information unless we specify otherwise at the point of collection.We also may disclose personally identifiable information you provide via this site to third parties, but only:

The collection, use, and disclosure of information contemplated in this Privacy Policy may involve a transfer of the information to jurisdictions located outside your country of residence that maynot have equivalent laws and rules regarding personally identifiable information. In these cases, you will be asked to consent to such transfers and disclosures in accordance with this Privacy Policy

1\. to carefully selected partners who have offers that may be of interest to you, provided you have requested such offers,in which case we will require such partners to agree to treat it in accordance with this Privacy Policy and use it for the same purposes.

2\. to contractors we use to support our business (such as fulfillment services, technical support, delivery services,and financial institutions), in which case we will require such third parties to agree to treat it in accordance with this Privacy Policy and use it for the same purposes;

3\. in connection with the sale,assignment, or other transfer of the business of this site to which the information relates, in which case we will require any such buyer to agree to treat it in accordance with this Privacy Policy and use it for the same purposes; or

4\. to respond to law enforcement requests or where required by applicable laws, court orders, or government regulations.

 **Public Areas**

Our site also has public areas such as chat rooms and message boards. Please remember that any information you share in these areas becomes public, so you should be careful about what you disclose. If you post comments about ModernMom products or services on our site, there’s a chance we’ll publish them for editorial purposes or in promotional advertising and/or marketing materials.

 **Access, Correction, and Deletion**

To keep personally identifiable information that you provide via this site accurate, current, and complete, please contact us as specified below and we will take appropriate steps to update or correct such information in our possession, or to delete your information from our contact list.

 **Security**

This site takes reasonable steps to protect personally identifiable information as you transmit it to our site and to protect such information from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. You should keep in mind that no Internet transmission is ever completely secure or error-free. In particular, e-mail sent to or from this site may not be secure.

 **Links to Other Web Sites**

This site may contain links or references to other Web sites to which this Privacy Policy does not apply. We encourage you to read the Privacy Policy of every Web site you visit.

 **Third Party Advertising**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. Please visit Connexity.com  if you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies.

 **Third Party Cookies**

In the course of serving advertisements to this site,  our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser.

 **AFFILIATE DISCLAIMER**

Some of the sections of this site will allow you to purchase different products and services online provided by other merchants, and not us. Some of the links that we post on our site are “affiliate links.” This means if you click on the link and purchase the item, we will receive an affiliate commission.*

We are not responsible for the quality, accuracy, timeliness, reliability or any other aspect of these products and services. In addition, a merchant will likely have privacy and data collection practices that are different from ours. If you make a purchase from a merchant on their site or on a site that we have posted a link to, the information obtained during your visit to that merchant’s online store or site, and the information that you give as part of the transaction, such as your name, e-mail address, street address, telephone number, and credit card number, may be collected the merchant and us. For more information regarding a merchant, its online store, its privacy policies, and/or any additional terms and conditions that may apply, visit that merchant’s website and click on its information links or contact the merchant directly.

We are a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for us to earn fees by linking to Amazon.com and affiliated sites.

 **How to Contact Us**

To keep your personally identifiable information accurate, current, and complete, please contact us as follows:

Mom, Inc. 15210 McKendree Ave Pacific Palisades, CA 90272-1239 United States
  *[CA]: California
